Oh
I think he might have not that much
little early offenders have been sold
out all through the country if you right
now have buttermilk crispy tenders and
air pots you're really doing well please
I love the to $4 apple pies yeah I'm
surprised you didn't get that yeah no
but honestly after the Arby's apple
turnovers today I ate too many no thank
you everyone just grabbed by grab a 10
now you give us a trip good check out my
10 not gonna see it yeah don't think I
don't think she was happy that we were
on the parcel
we didn't you love I love M&M McFlurry
to ever never employees are great
demonstration unit here's our license
plate for the guys to go we did get it
to go they messed up our order it's
alright though sorry it's the same thing
because we took you to go anyway what I
didn't law unlock the car guys yeah no
look look they're cold how long should
we keep them cold for well we got Supra
lights
oh I can't even get up my know get some
hold on the periscope alright okay no
sauce in the car alright I'm handing you
all back to Vivian hold the drive to oh
no I like going in real good to pee too
alright so you see our destination is
the Lacroix Wellness Center what's that
yeah
what do so many things packing cubes are
guys this is our last periscope there'll
be no showing yeah just reflections on
the tour we would guys coming eyes not
shutting down
there is no way in hell it's all in jail
to be honest let's be real because let
me tell you who I draw a life
inspiration from captain on a fake show
in a movie called Galaxy Quest hmm his
saying is
never give up never surrender yeah nice
that's the truth never give up we know
we're in a real place because there's an
Applebee's here who wears the Tesla
supercharger someone just mentioned they
saw it and I can't find it do you see
one here oh there it is we tweet our
location
enormous Kobe's 50 people doing it for
last backup no I really there's no
showing on this one no emotional
blackmail we've never given up we're
gonna win as much as I might want to
give up my life would be a lot easier
but you feel my life could be so easy
you guys feel shame I don't even think I
feel shame and guilt I don't really feel
those things what I would feel is just
kind of like bored we're done the truth
is stolen things exciting life is when
new things come out of nowhere
yeah but can we open this group I think
we'll get more in life for the viewer
there we go we really have any new
experiences on this tour they'd like to
share
to a deep dark hole we talk about life
we talked about the Oh reactionary
action is
that's cool
question existence question it's just a
new way of thinking about that
what else
we did talk about the silent scope
section yeah we did we were like these
parents were concerned we're really
being real in this Samuels for watching
right
what else know
look George did you have any reflections
you wanted to say no I really just like
what I was saying yesterday about I'm
not sure I want to be a rapper when I
grow up I'm not sure I could go around
the country from place to place and
perform the same songs over and over
again
it's kind of what it feels like I don't
know that's something that's always been
really hard
to like do the same thing twice and not
before the second time it's good
ah ah
I'm not really cut out scoring around
there are rappers not
their studio rapper
now two more like this kind of art
invisible
you know we probably will do this next
year again
um the car will drive better blossom
corporate sponsorship
but no don't-don't-don't feel pressure
to buy our products we're not actually
going out of business only if you want
it you guys know what our return policy
is like an identity we are running low
and that's my pressure going on yeah
let's go
Scopus did you guys have any reflections
wanna laugh to nuggets
it was the fear of um Oh bang but almost
dying and then ending up in this small
little oasis called America 457 you guys
we can't even stop we're shilling for
things
yeah I was all-in then out now that call
in I just ordered a new car
thank you yeah but not with a shell
we're not we really would not even still
have a little America genuine how do you
separate that from shilling right what's
the definition
how can you even communicate genuine
emotion but you genuinely feel love for
little America yeah but but that's the
thing like eight how can you communicate
the difference right in a world so
saturated with fake news
is it real what is a show on oysters
that worth an accomplice of a hawker
gambler or swindler
I mean who acts as an enthusiastic
customer to entice or encourage other
yeah so it has to be deceptively
promoting something we're not shooting
there's a song Green Tigers by the world
is a beautiful place them no longer
afraid to die and they have a have a
line I really like
here's why you said simulation a little
bit but um you know can you still call
it a country if all the states are
broken can you still call it a business
if all you're doing stealing
how I feel a lot of
right do you have to close
in the same way you know the end coded
driving cars moment and coded simulators
won't win for the same reason it's good
it's a vision X graphics instead of
vision graphics is still
and try to get all the last education
reflect on reflected anymore the last
nugget how many buckets all last nugget
huh which one good luck doing that port
whose realness
reflect on this year try to write a song
about it
do you have tea
because I hope you're seeing that sunset
man I'm getting good at Philco yeah
there's always kind of depressing to
drive to the east for this reason we're
driving away from the light yeah
Oh
that's these day life I mean yeah for
like
president do any get home
go to New York City
ready for my final York
we should not go for a little bit an
urban Scott
turn your intern
you know my New York City
I know miss Chicago Miami Chicago I love
you
it's real
yeah way more than that stuff
with SF is you have you have no
diversity
there's very little diversity in San
Francisco yeah
diversity of thought no I mean it's
absolutely true right and then what you
get when you lack diversity is extremism
kind of what you see in San Francisco
it's sad you don't have this in New York
New York I think things are pretty well
balanced so extreme physicians are
ridiculed as they should be and you know
everyone's kind of kind of pushed to the
middle and a common ground you really do
have a model
clémence ground between New Yorkers we
were in San Francisco you just have
each other
something else we're talking about I
think you can look at the two sides
political spectrum this year one Cypress
maybe driven by a hate for life
immigrants entered the other side was
driven by a hate for an arranged and I
think both of these are proxies for well
what's going to be hated in 2020 and
it's going to be technology
you're already starting to see it was a
wired article this morning I think
that's gonna pick up we're gonna start
to see real nature of Technology I am
deep down you know curious as to why
if AI does take all of your jobs
isn't that a good thing
I'm just an out-of-touch startup bro
right
I am back
I never said I was a good guy I'm just a
guy
that's good sometimes
I think yeah long little wing it has a
great track the end of the car 2/3 don't
get it where he goes into this it's just
like you know I am just human and I
don't know if that's it hair really good
or inherently bad
offense
behind
[Music]
but has-been
things will also get much cheaper
yeah I mean just the theory is about
like once once they're weird once the
machines are cheaper than a we just ate
a whole chickens worth of nugget five
dollars right so the same is gonna be
true when they I replace a little
jealous right sovaldi does everyone feel
like kinda Hina fall from those Nuggets
if you disgusting little disgusting kind
of fall right I got good calories it's
me I know I got to eat vegetables scope
Green's Supremes yeah it's hard to eat
green thumb
astronaut roughly yeah likewise
McDonald's was selling raw kale you can
talk about whether it's excited so
that's one of the theories I've heard I
wonder if or if it's really not what
people are going to buy
the expensive part is that it goes
it does go bad it's a lot easier to ship
nuggets her milk and chicken tenders are
out of stock all over America
where we went doing once
I think so our trucks do but a lot of
them are 24 volts don't blog and panda
you can't act
there's a notch in the 2400 yeah I think
I can I don't know what the bus is yeah
I don't know what the bus is on our
planes it's not that many interface no
it shows a lot of ECU's like Emily I
want wasted like a hooker seven like the
77 right yeah I was thinking like a
small play goes like A to Z airplane is
probably like an old Cessna 172 yeah it
was playing through oh then that's
literally it's like she thought there's
a linkage yeah I don't even know if
there's hydraulic boost I think that
you're making the flap go off by pushing
on
yeah no I mean a modern 747 polyansky
something like that probably yeah
I think ellika
I love taffy you wanted water Joe in
Minneapolis we could have visited water
Joe no not like a system not like an old
Cessna 172 sheriff sheriff O's new play
it's like if you you're talking like a
big jumbo jets yeah they're fly-by-wire
well some people like the thing about
wire is - meaning like piece of piano
wire controller control services on
small planes are literally a linkage I
think
maybe new ones a different
you know I think it like all we lost the
rudder okay climb out kind of just like
push on a little bit right works
so we fixed it now look I can press the
cruise control button to change or reset
the health bar I was a little change we
made
trying to get this release out tonight
or maybe tomorrow
realness not silent
it's not like the periscope last night
maybe this is pretty good last
what do you think's there
pretty fine
people pretty quiet
too much steering on this time
alors
it's first it's like it possible to see
the wheels of just showing
no you're not quietly you're asking some
questions but like you know like how are
we going to support cleans it was like
no you know what actually so much really
built so in small planes the number one
cause of crash is controlled flight into
terrain and that is exactly what it
sounded like you crashed into a mountain
in a completely working plane at first
you think you know that was really dumb
why'd you crash into the mountain and
the problem is this and look and you see
a mountain in the distance right you
can't exactly estimate sort of what your
climb rate is you're like okay we'll fly
over now
but say the mountain has like you know
2,000 feet over a thousand feet over and
your climb rate is only like 400 feet
per minute
well if you only have two minutes until
impact that's not gonna work so what you
really want to do is turn around um
somebody should make an app that you can
run that just you know we have great
terrain maps this is such you know such
a preventable accident
I'm not selling you know of every
conversation and everything
did what they say currently they like
you we don't know they didn't like
sounds like they did we got we got
someone out there who was team v
notice anything different
some states Nevada it had issues to
match the right lane in Nevada was about
three times as thick as
the model
waitjust some more predictable you
couldn't read the code for it it's
pretty well-documented they watch you're
entitled to your own opinion but you're
not entitled to your own facts
no don't worry I'm not gonna bid
I do been the boss how riddles I'm
driving maybe our city
[Music]
the truth about self-driving this is
pretty boring
actually like us working well safe
driving is boring
what did you name this George
maybe 1 million pairs go the last one
the last one asked the last month one
the last periscope heart to her
you lock that that's Honda CB lawyer
dude do me
which way to him oh I block people on
Twitter piss me off yeah okay
thing is like oh they're just out there
you know they like just likely live even
no you can't kind of be okay I mean
maybe we can you might be right but
you're not adding anything to the
conversation by saying right just saying
no you can now if you have like critical
feedback that's always welcome but if
you just have a me and blocked Peters
get blocked
critical feedback is always welcome if
you're funny oh yeah then you have stops
exhausting I would love to see
even about you cero there that was I'm
gonna call myself out if you like juice
arrow we applaud you for trying oh you
know like that was like anti shelling
right I don't even want an anti show
that would mean you're talking about
well the truth is healing truthful it
was like antes Schilling is like no to
be honest like a juice arrow I had to
pick great products for so the green the
green box you were referring to as the
calibration box it didn't convey that
much information to the user so it's
been removed the you up you I am grade
of 0.4
that's what first pass in Rochester
Rochester pink since Roger that there's
only one crime just there exist yeah and
if you miss it you're going all the way
across what were the goals of the tour
do you get really good
so the real trick is be honest guys do
and we did something that's the real
goal and I'll selling stuff some stuff
some stuff like obviously like it
doesn't like you next year we're
actually gonna start running ads for
things welcome to being a real startup
right gonna run ads we're gonna track
know our spent to get a conversion able
even by light Instagram ads
one of the best ways to get
to convert yeah like marketing it's just
like gotta do it right it's part of our
it's just part of a machine that's I was
all shot out a shout out uh Scott
Alexander slate Star coax some great
blog posts
talking about like mala and how we're
all slaves tomorrow and how like you
know everybody might want the world to
be better but it's hard to actually make
that move elegant to you Kowski just
came out with a book about this to
inadequacy and equilibria or something
I forget the exact title but if it don't
go go check it out it just kind of talks
about like even if you have a hundred
people who all could take collective
action to make the world better each if
each individual is incentivized to do
something else and well the collective
action doesn't get taken and now don't
scream communism please don't scream
communism at all what if we just all
workers in the world United communism
has to kill more people than any other
ideology erased
nice we got a super like running Alex -
is that is that something we unlocked
with super dancer
like asking a parent who's a favorite
child
our favorite investor
um also like about these about these
like other meta things like the dan
Carlin's like stark or solicited a the
point that I want you to take away is
not to like look at my opinion and be
like I agree with it because he said it
what I like about these resources is
they kind of give or they've given me
new ways to think
give me new ways to think about problems
and if you come to different conclusions
that's fine I just you know I think this
end of this little I quit questions with
Suraj thing
at its our machine learning conference
and if there's one way the world could
be better let's make the world more kind
of self-reflect
should everyone
you should have something like basic
knowledge to be able to use like Excel
yeah I mean that's code yeah just like
algorithms yeah everybody should
understand like the basic ideas in the
field I so slow good yeah i Kansas City
makerspace that I lived which was um if
you don't know how to fix it you don't
really own it
we've annotated by who and where the
scooty elementary school we went to the
kids are learning to code
it's a good way I don't know why I
started when I was really young
you pick it up easier when your kids
like a second language yeah
well not exactly no coding is even more
of you speak french french and english
and not that far wouldn't speak French
doors are leaking of course I could
learn French easier Michael are Chinese
now alright maybe talk about like like
if you're an English speaker like
learning like friend to Spanish or you
know language like that are much easier
entire German or Russian which are even
easier to learn than like Chinese
Japanese
like I was on
dams are like yes
I like the Bourdieu company a lot
I think trains the future no I mean like
agenda system transportation
yeah we have to get away from this
companies that are using psychological
tricks to make people addicted
on Twitter addict I confess
okay something funny like I'm actually
kind of sad about my Twitter addiction
George is all in your power just
and this to an extent like of course it
is right but you know here's the thing
about at bat attics if you talk to
people who are addicts drug addicts
they'll tell you that's right say that
it's all in your power to stop and it is
but the truth is they are still getting
something out of their addiction or they
would stop right I am still getting
something out of my Twitter addiction
and that's why I don't stop
survey Facebook - right like if you
truly were getting nothing out of it if
you truly got nothing right
imagine the drugs stopped working
using the trucks who feel fast alright
you scream and complain about that but
the fundamental you are getting
something out of it wouldn't be an
addict
realities for
it's better than the alternative right
then you can go you can go look at your
own made-up world
and even if it did I mean
well that's a decision that everyone's
gonna have to make probably sooner than
we think about whether you want to be
water I don't know refer to the drug use
not you
realities forward that's why couple use
drugs
as long
or there's some aspect of reality they
can't cope with
man
okay yeah I told him that they were
computers I taught them about physics
why are having a diet might be the same
thing
these questions doesn't think about
philosophy philosophy encompasses
everything that science has not yet to
come up with an answer to right we used
to use philosophy to determine you know
what everything was made of go back to
Aristotle and now well
use chemistry
and you know wouldn't we need you talks
about like God being dead I mean what
God was replaced by it was kind of an
Enlightenment view of the world
he was a rational view of the world
obviously the reason the Sun rises is
not because there's a man in a chariot
pulling ahead but because
now the earth is spinning right this is
this is a lot of you know what you want
to talk about where I get a lot of this
worldview from it's like less wrong and
rationality kind of stuff
although it may be simple foul hats
we're to periodical Bob Martin stuff
my comment on Mars was a I'll go there
when there were five star hotels there
talking not necessarily because all I
need to stay on the 5:2 hotel I would
rough it on Mars man actually won a
Martian bench but um no that would just
say something about like where the kind
of safety and reasonability of the
journey are the places that I want to
explore are necessarily on Mars I show a
lot more
do I think I'll visit Mars my life
had to bet on it 10% chance
I would just speak
if I give space Mars similar chances
it's gonna be like a one-year trip
this
temporal difference learning or
something
Moonves or Mars best first you guys look
at the lights
my fries Jimin
not really
Oh
then explicit on like types of software
development for management's I should
maybe it's worthwhile to learn more
about that
right now we just kind of cold we have
integration tests
there we agree of unit tests and things
like API is some of those functions
under Lionel Island we have been
complete hardware in the loop
integration test
in the house
you know
and then we have our army of beta
testers you bets
which ourselves
for cars
he's reader is radar
look at cameras just from a roll and you
don't understand what the sensor is they
are incredibly high bandwidth cheap
available
or as they they don't really compare to
anything else just because a smart
you know become so she yeah I mean this
big there's big market pressures driving
better and better cameras
I would turn
but if you are consumer if you want to
connect yeah we obviously encourage
people to fax but we're not at the level
where we're providing consumer support
camera see
or it drives better at night
because there's a ton more contract
came on a road trip with us
oh no this time of day is always kind of
depressing
yeah I kind of boring do like long walks
on the beach
there was a 7k target we'll do a blog
post to forget what don't tell them that
now we're not even chilling it's real
you know no we really would do it it's
okay I mean I'd like something I'd like
to see yeah give me that God mode and
I'll do it
your camera's invented cars for more
data
really limited byte data
we're limited by engineering
we're not even limited by engineers
it's very hard you know a lot of people
think most kind of food engineering is
kind of a creative endeavor right and if
you want to creative endeavor to get
done faster if you want like an artist
man produce more paintings produce more
paintings you couldn't really hire more
people you couldn't really give him more
money you couldn't really give him more
paint it's just kind of done when it's
done kind of what this stuff is too
we're working we have ideas fantastic
the guy said Kansas City makerspace
he was talking
College gets their his advice was about
you know when you build something you
build it because your taste that's much
higher than what's available right so
you know the system that comes on the
Toyota our tastes were higher than it
really wanted we we have higher
expectations for what it should be then
we build this thing that keeps you the
lane lines some people are or there come
up to us and they're like oh this looks
incredible but our taste has been raised
you have like the taste where's there's
what you're capable is always kind of
catching up when you build the thing
with the bed better taste taste Rises
but you become more capable if you time
but we return
it's like I don't know man I get so
frustrated when this thing doesn't work
it should work way better and like next
year it will work way better but I
promise you on next year's self-driving
car awareness to her
it'll probably do it'll be better but
I'll still be mad about how bad it is
right
and even when it's perfect even when
it's what it's level for you know we're
gonna get like like you know any any
sort of crash any sort of minor mishap
but it still has to be better I'm not
saying it has to get hurt a ship right
they say if you're not embarrassed by
what you're shipping your ship too late
just a one of our one of our points one
of our novice
some of our employees aren't office
our respect
so what is the end goal of the company
to win self-driving cars
we're talking cars it's not even like
that's not even like there sometimes
you'll see it you'll see the way I
taught you'll see kind of in the mindset
of man
and I'll say it and I do understand that
what people take that to me is not
exactly what I mean when we say it but I
want to solve this I guess I can say
this I'm gonna solve the problem
I wanna see the solution when I thought
I solved the problem we're seeing the
solution
I'd rather solve it myself it's like a
it's like a math problem in the back of
the textbook but what's cool is this
isn't contrived doing a math problem in
the back of a textbook you know but no
Donald Knuth would put I would put math
problems in his textbook that were like
unsolved problems it's kind of feel-good
who'd even have an unsolved problem
free to Hofmann's okay
no I say that to troll more than
anything else I don't know I don't
really have an opinion
I don't know if this is a question or
statement
[Music]
level four has to be everywhere well
double food is everything everywhere
that's level five level four can
literally just be on one route
now I'm
I was more honest
maybe these sort of to happy I wish they
were more honest and aggressive
your sensors are really
and this is what Google does right
Google can take an idea and they can
build the best one of it I've worked at
Google a bunch of times and this is
really what the culture brings out
you can see with crawl g-man
search
they're not so good when they try to do
new things Google glass to be honest
it's not even Google glass was kind of a
bad product
yeah they're not not that innovative
there there there are people who go like
the last mile fortunately in a weird way
and this is kinda out of the world is
today Google just buys up startups
the world is Google's Innovation Lab
what is what is the end goal for comma
live forever
people
company and that's kind of a goal end
goal of every
stupid in what is
operation operation
mobile it gives like a great
presentation at cvpr about about vision
about real stuff and then they give a
whole presentation that isn't about how
to make driving safer but about how to
make driving provably safe so we can
determine who has liable
talk to my reason interview about the
size of a pie
why don't we just put you know make the
12 in this case make the fire crashes
smaller right and not worry about who as
much slice
I'm talking similarity well first you've
got to define that term I was 15 I first
read le as any Kowski stuff
yeah it's
the first year about doubling of
computing
and the idea is if you build a system
that's as powerful as humanity this is
called Moore's law which says humanity
doubles the power of computers every
into the speed of computers or the
number transistors on a die or doubles
every 18 months right but if it's the
machines doubling their own power every
18 months the next double it will take
nine months and the next doubling will
take four point-five banks would take
2.25
and then 36 months you have a
singularity where they're doubling kind
of infinitely fast it's kind of like The
Tortoise and the hare problem
there's that definition and there's the
definition of the obsolescence of
humanity which is computers are capable
of doing every job
you have to talk about which definition
they're talking about and what you want
to know
probably yeah
this is they banned people from riding
horses on the slope
now you need clothes courses right just
like cars
people with us all the way to looks
awesome I cast yet something
look that one do it
yeah I'm so working with the OEMs is
incredibly difficult
our structure
I'm not sure that is the effort all
I think you have to think about how else
I think entering at the dealership level
might be the appropriate sort of place
with the arteries where the dealer's
perception of that idea they enjoyed it
they liked the idea obviously they
wanted to be more consumer on this
course but that probably is the way
does this approach women
here's a question wall of wind right
just the other approaches are in some
ways more predictable if you're talking
about the build a car and ship a car
approach the fastest company from
inception to shipping a standard
production vehicle I think was Tesla I
think it took them seven years so that's
how long it would take a company if they
started today to build a car maybe it's
a little bit easier with electric maybe
they can do it in four or five but it's
still a huge challenge so if companies
start today or started last year it
started two years ago I think we beat
them if they're trying to build cars now
then there's companies who are trying to
work with OEMs so you look at like Volvo
have these drive pilot program that they
were planning to make you this year
they've pushed it back to 2021 which
seems to be that date that a lot of
these car manufacturers are saying
again I think we win like but we don't
mean I feel they solve the problem with
it
the truth is most people that will ask
me questions about like does the public
perception of these systems matter and
in reality public perception is a
lagging indicator of quality if you have
good quality somehow our society is
fairly efficient at disseminating
information if you have bad quality the
same thing applies step one
build a good system do you have to solve
the problem and I think it's solved
maybe two or three years
that beats out anybody really trying to
work with OEMs if you believe they're
2021 and anybody trying to build their
own car then there's this third approach
the third approach is maybe the way Moe
of approach where they're building
self-driving with a building right share
networks
the thing about ride-sharing networks is
you have to operate super unprofitably
until the minute you solve the problem
now if solving the problem were very
very very predictable but we knew due to
some kind of you know inexorable law
that the problem would be solved by 2020
and exactly what sensors in compute
would be required if we knew that then
the ride-sharing approach would probably
win because if we knew that best fit
would be easy the world could get
together multiple trillion dollars to
build out the entire network subsidize
it do it all with human drivers and then
2020 you flip the switch but because of
that uncertainty scene I tend to believe
about that long
which was
salt is important
can we get an MTV Cribs
hey if you know someone at MTV Cribs
yeah what which level so
doesn't really like the levels are
stupid I guess I am talking about level
4 the levels are really just a liability
question it's like oh the Supreme Court
thing where it's like you know
pornography right it's hard to define
but you'll know it when you see it it's
the same thing kind of what self-driving
system is right
you'll know it when it's solved he'll
type in a destination it'll go there and
it's highly unlikely to make a mistake
better than you try it statistically
better than humans so I guess that is
level 4
the levels are kind of off
it's all about the number two
significance
after 75
one way road trip
all right so what car should we buy for
next year self-driving car later in the
sponsored by sponsored by silver car Oh
silver car might actually sponsor nope
notice that we were definitely on lease
you'd have to pay me to drive across the
country to Subaru attend again I'm an
anti shelling I don't really have
anything wrong with Subaru WRX as a nice
no way I'm taking a Lambo to some of the
places we went while the Lambo and the
snow and ice and stuff say fours are
small wheel drive
we could definitely work definiteiy a
different route next year but yeah we're
gonna do the same sort of thing drive
across the country
that's sponsored I mean no no no I
predict I predict a big things for combo
look at how much has changed me here one
year ago we had
barely even to be honest I think we
didn't start to get people until January
we had open pilot 0.1 was really
unusable it would crash every couple
minutes like just software would crash
the neo was was was janky they were kind
of hard to get her to get that board
made I used to have to like step or get
up like by the court and by the cables
on itself this cable was a hazard what
we saw this year we saw a neo driven we
saw la timer felt the board's
yeah I don't know across the
international border
no don't think so
you know you can look at you and Joshua
Brown's death and lifetime and obviously
you know it's sad but statistically
safe for safer it's as safe as are safer
than humans assuming that there's a
human watching in conjunction with the
system right in the Joshua Brown case
you know there was no human watching
human was on check Harry Potter as
that's what's believed I mean that's
just true right so you know with all
these systems really pay attention at
all times you have to and you're gonna
have to for a while but
I'm not really sure how you define human
to be a little careful with uploading
this gets this gets real and sort of no
no no why our heading is very different
from uploading
I don't know it's all a little bit too
far away to think about back thinking
about self-driving cars again I mean
we've always talked about watching the
driver
yeah
what's up we will have to yeah water
working super products from marketing
product so yeah I mean he on
we have to check I'm not really sure
whether the front-facing camera can see
you or not it's gonna be you pops we
talk about flipping Tesla a p1 couldn't
see you Tesla a p2 as a driver facing
camera yeah slam on the brakes
well as hard as it can so we would
decelerate with 0.3 G of breaking and
then I would press the brakes even
harder get up to 1g
breaking is almost always safer than
swerving breaking is almost always the
right choice much for a really confident
miss or well like he's just swerving
like around like our car that you know
is not going to move is fine but
swerving around deer in the breaks you
sort of try to predict the deers motion
you end up hitting him yeah without
animals braking is the right choice
usually
there's a black cat he can't stop that's
why then we hit the black cat hoping
pilot won't slam on the brakes for a cat
sorry John neither would you
Oh
so I mean what you really wanna do is
like if minimum wage laws increase do
you see in areas where minimum wage laws
are kind of high like in Europe or in
California they'll see that McDonald's
has replaced a lot of the ordering with
those computer screens right so minimum
increased minimum wage will expedite the
replacement of humans with machines
why are their employees of fast food
restaurants probably cheaper
some of those things are kind of like
anything where you have to like use your
hand and complex ways robotics isn't
quite there use such as complet
multitasked yeah well it's hard to like
it's also much harder to train a robot
than to train a person
I'm error recovery is tricky you can
probably do it no and you don't whatever
you'd also have to look at what the
breakdown of operating fast-food
franchises how much of the cost is human
labor
yes
yeah well yeah so that's the idea right
you can you can slam and steer now again
your car still has traction you have to
ask the question of you know started
racing a little bit you have to ask the
question of where you want to use your
grip
do you want to use your grip to brake
and steer or do you want to use your
grip to try to do both both is almost
always the worst choice right because
they are getting less braking like sure
you can brake and steer but you're
getting less braking if you're trying to
steal now using some of your friction in
order to steam
there
yeah well that depends on your traction
control system the one in this car is
really good
I had a Nissan 350z I used to ride
around Rochester that traction control
system was terrible obviously to that
early 2000 it was a 2008 and it would
get which it would increase the
oscillations and wouldn't dampen who's
really poorly done this one is this is
so much better
see I mean yeah bad ones do that good
ones ones don't
I love something related to the Festiva
thing it's so crazy that like they get a
check
okay yeah like this is larger here's our
Sochi you know that they could just like
put them at they're doing this they're
doing this at all the fast casual
restaurants and there's actually one
startup and killing doing this now you
go to you've got like an Applebee's are
an Olive Garden
if Carter even if Carter is at the table
they've cards on the table and even
worse the things like try to upsell you
one little game
I think you're sitting maybe not maybe
it's just a work day for for yeah no but
this is huge and all the fast-casual it
started cold like a hand or something
there's one company who's made a killing
doing this and all of these like Chili's
macaroni grill all of these that's
called fast casual
airplanes landing on a highway and
and these edge cases are extremely
extremely rare what do you do if there's
an airplane landing on the highway well
you probably definitely do something
much smarter than a human because you do
not damage human might you know panic
stare at the airplane driving
honestly what you do most of the times
if weird scenarios is break here don't
panic right um these scenarios are not
this is the same thing with the trolley
problem like it's not real this is not
the dilemma that anybody in the real
world has faced and this is I almost I
don't blame people for thinking this I
really blame the news I really blame the
news for making these extremely rare
events in common
and what they do and this is this is
actually like thinking like this if
there's anything you could be doing
that's more productive but you're not
even sure are but it's killing people
right because to be honest had a most
car accidents happen I'm a chef people
aren't looking people are texting drunk
people are asleep fix that we're talking
educators they still say anything else
look at that's right bro stay on the
rope
I know exactly right but but it's also
okay
I don't know he might be the wind
you see trucks do this and I think they
only do it when it's
oh wow imagine they actually ship some
things too I heard you can sign up for
do they have a price and can you
actually send that money for free
yeah like like to be honest if they're
taking like just a one or all down
payment but now it's the announcement
they announce all great it's just to
raise more money it's honestly just to
raise more money it's a PR stunt unless
there's a price and a ship game it
didn't even look like real photos it
looked like render hey look like
renderings right like at least like
Tesla might announce something in three
years away but light of its artists they
all ship it in five years and so knows
driving someone was driving one right
see that's what I mean like it's just
okay it's just fake and everyone should
be better at like realizing just open
I'm a direct has some trouble
better surprisingly good
what about a Rolling Stones good
about about about Mashpee biggest dam
yeah oh my run about a scam look was
that no and wait is that was a scammer I
think oh did they review it magic leave
actually no look matted early reviews so
what I've seen with magic leap is they
continually like promise this this of
that hey guys you know remember when I
said we were to launch the comma one we
open sourced it all by the end of the
year and like here we are a year later
and like got a comma here
a lot nicer that's not top right Koreans
that create just the screen it's
important to chef it's important to be
real
in some ways the only way to kind of
express yourself differently is to
counter signal
Galia is his book talks about this to
really analyze encounter signaling
oh they're probably can't talk about it
yeah say all of it they're all probably
have like insane it that's right
whatever you have scams you haven't seen
in today's do we make a place on it I P
agreement is to prevent us from being
sued there's very little in common it's
truly non-disclosure if somebody leaked
what the pigeon was we ordered they'd be
fired a medium may be fired immediately
just like the person who leaked midnight
black oh god guys if I could fire myself
as CEO calm I would have done the demo
many times no I mean like magic
[Music]
bad like she has the positive like I
love like you know the only reason
people think this is impossible is
because they think you know they don't
try hard enough or like anything is
possible if you believe in yourself and
like it's a nice sentiment like it's not
even that you beam is impossible right
you being this actually you could build
it right you say they do show those
things they don't show anything real
like the current flow and power flow to
the device yeah it was really that's
what you really want to do anyone gets a
watt meter up right come on those little
USB so us beads I'm welcome to charge
either one you know what you could
probably get the current up you could
probably even design the thing to be
safe right yeah but I feel like uv-vis
caught so much in this like we have to
kind of prove ourselves to the world
been saying this for so long so in poker
this concept was called me a
committed
yeah right like I've already put a lot
of money in the pot this might already
be like a kind of losing hand like I
kind of think I'm gonna lose the hand
like you know calling his raise isn't
really worth it but I'm gonna do it
that's unplug what should they do when
they realize like we can't really build
this what we showed is a rendering when
we went through investors yeah what do
you do after you collected 50 million I
don't know I don't know what you they
don't have I mean it's not like they can
give the money back
right like this code and they could get
it back at a loss they could be like let
this be a lesson
yeah but like the whole point is it's
not even that you bees is impossible
it's just incredibly impractical
charging cellphones using ultrasonic
power is incredibly impractical
I can set your teeth
oh hello dragons actor um one of the
guys from nullified in Omaha and he sets
up the new Meridian as my jersey still
plays ETF's I'm like really anymore and
then he said we don't really buy their
CTFs have a minute
I thought that was like a really
brilliant way to express kind of what I
think about CTF now it's
it's too much like okay there's these
kind of problems these kind of problems
these kind of problems these kind of
problems you drill on them to get faster
at them and ironically as much as I
talked about winning the real reason I
played CTFs was to learn and I just
wasn't learning as much anymore and I'm
still not learning as much I've come
back and tried a few problems
occasionally but it doesn't have a sort
of novelty that I feel that it used
anyway like just let me take a little
quick aside here
driving the boatman pilot well he is a
great experience I'm not even chilling
have been we've been we've been driving
for it for an hour
like
everybody already when they're driving
let's driving fate into their
unconscious I'm sure everyone's had this
experience where they were driving on a
highway and they realized wow I've just
traveled an hour and I haven't really
thought about driving much that was kind
of the experience that I just had right
even when I say things like oh I'm
correcting a little bit from this turn
that's all of the unconscious level
someway the machine learning bottle in
there is like working with the model
that's in my mind
just something we have to think about
what we do model objects
study something else that's real we
approached Afghan I wanted to speak
there this year and they said no
they said no they're like you know we
can we can't just we can't just pick
speakers because they're famous and I
respect that and if it comes from like a
really honest place and they're saying
that you know I wish them well
but you know I don't like to question
people's and intentions but
what I've seen I'm not gonna question
their intentions but I will talk about
what I've seen at DEFCON right and what
I've seen it a lot of conferences maybe
it's like the death of subculture
defconn's started out as a real hacker
subculture conference right
and I'll talk about we'll talk about it
to city inclusivity is great inclusivity
of
you know please join my subculture you
know if you're interested in hacking if
you are genuinely interested in hacking
we would love to have you and we want
you to learn we want you to be better
but what we don't want and what you have
to watch out for is people who
show up at DEFCON and don't like half
the culture right
if you don't like it
there's the global culture you could try
to change the global culture but let
people have their subcultures but I kind
of see things like DEFCON drifting away
from subculture and that was kind of you
know apparent to me when they didn't
want me to speak so I don't know I don't
know about be back at DEFCON
maybe maybe I'll show up for a few for a
few interesting meetings but just kind
of my thoughts on it what where's the
next thing right what's the next thing
and that's something I ask that I have
to grapple with my life right like like
the death of Nikes hacker subculture
maybe it's I don't know maybe it still
exists somewhere but to be fair like
that was the 90s right
the subculture body in life you know
hackers with Angelina Jolie like that
was great these are the things I grew up
watching right
to that you watch sneakers you want to
watch wargames hack remove easy
yeah be there was kind of question of
what's next yes
sorry we mean an accusing DEFCON support
if you're having a good time by all
means I keep on going
the first my pants of fog that's my
bantha
no computers allowed you know what you
know what no no no no no we shouldn't
discriminate like that I mean the
problem wasn't that they were a bomb the
problem is that they were repeating what
other people were saying they did add an
emoji value to be honest yeah I could
build a bot that yeah
[Music]
yeah I mean Bojack has to kind of find a
way to move on in some ways I didn't
like the fourth season at Bojack because
he
no no I shouldn't that's not really a
spoiler right and that that's like more
that's kind of bad I always like to know
if it's over but that is kind of what
bojack's about it's very uh you know in
with the cultural zeitgeist so Jack
should be
I've been cleared to see Molson
that's baby come on say it was happy
right it was like a glimmer of more Hope
than at the end of others
I have a saying a lot to mix up seven
seasons of house taught me that people
don't change
so
ha
I think about that it am i capable of
changing when will win will when will I
become a cultural relic
what you do is it
what would I do is uber CEO
um
or Travis back and let him do it you
know what I would I would sit him down
first and here's the advice that I would
give to him
never apologize you have done so much
for good for the world Hoover has done
so much good how many lives and breaths
probably saved
people who didn't drag on a drum
and if you know there's just such a
there's such an end when I'm like wow I
just I don't know that's things that
make me less hopeful for the future
where there's some cultural problems at
Hoover maybe I wasn't there but when you
look at Hoover as a force right not to
here to speak about anyone to no
experience at but when you look at
goobers force on the world and goobers
impact on my life and Hoover's impact on
all the people who they've employed
right you can talk about well uber
drivers you know they all hate you
no one's forcing you to do it yeah it's
an opportunity literally you're you're
given an opportunity where you kind of
didn't happen so yeah what what I do is
Hooper CEO if I think for a while about
what I want to say to Travis uh-huh sit
him down for an hour tell him my
thoughts listen to his opinions then
probably regardless of what he says say
welcome back
if you what you want to do it maybe I
don't know but what if they lose a
million dollars every year yeah and you
look at what's happening no I don't know
and you know what it's so sad if we lose
ride sharing in the world I think we
lose it but we'll play it will pay
triple the price well no see that's the
problem right leg I'm okay with paying
triple the price but not everybody is
then and then and then it would go up or
what I'm not okay with is waiting 18
minutes for an uber right and then it's
okay and then it's over and then it's
over if they like you you need to have
sort of a critical density of
ride-sharing but in order for the
network to work
new the new of the new model of
architecture the new model architecture
is much more holistic much more toward
the original dream of coming a I event
and learning this model is not very on
into edge now the lanes are we're not
hand coded they're extracted by an
automatic ground-truthing engine but the
automatic ground something engine is
hand code I even want to move away from
that
No so I'm kind of bearish on dedicated
AI chipsets and here's why
when you look at a CPU die and when you
look at how many so so so it's it's
multiplied accumulates right multiply
two numbers and like accumulates that's
the basic kind of DSP operation that you
need for a matrix multiplication which
is what neural networks are you look at
the CPUs die and you realize really only
like two or three percent of the
transistors are dedicated to doing this
so there's clearly a room for a 30%
improvement right at the same process
size in the same power
so using CPUs for neural network sucks
or bad idea when we look at a GPUs die
you see that like sixty percent of the
GPU already has the transistors kind of
where you want
now you can do things like pipelining
veteran dedicated hardware than you can
on GPU
but it's not gonna be a 10x improvement
it's gonna be a two or three exit the
truth is that's the kind of improvement
you could get some soft breath
so I'm bearish I'm dedicated they had
chipsets and I'm bullish on GPU DSPs and
things that are a bit more
general-purpose
because yeah because a lot of it
transistors for anything
for the purpose you would use them
Florida dedicated chips in any way
honestly I really want to stick with
smartphone hardware for as long as I can
well next year's thing to be based
around a smartphone maybe see see how
things shake up this here
oh that's not so we're never gonna put
policy in the back
you're like cruising waiting opening
policy
and like at some point it doesn't really
matter right
also the people think that there are
regulatory barriers to level 4 there
aren't some states you can already put
your car on the road
no people it's just fine I mean it's a
liability question right obviously
you're liable then for what that car
does there's no driver in the car detect
liability there's very little advantage
to do against state by state
there might be an advantage to doing it
Road type by row type but then that kind
of isn't level for its level three you
banned low quality users we won't
discriminate whether their community
repetition Boulder yeah well yeah I
guess fine right funny really funny you
gotta be fun really calm and don't rid
of that crap this isn't even anti
shelling so many sucks I don't know just
like kind of it you know what not even
gonna be nice to something
I'm not allowed to discuss my settlement
meeting but I am allowed to discuss the
meeting we had after the settlement
where I met with some engineers and if
they were gonna be lawyers they wanted
me to tell me how they did it they
really wanted me to like do free
security testing on the PlayStation for
them happy to talk about it to be honest
especially if they're engineers they're
like the guys who built the security
system
no after you solve a puzzle it's really
fun to talk with the guy who wrote the
puzzle
so ya know I went to a room and uh
they're engineers we just don't we just
gotta talked about all PlayStation
security
stakes how things could have done
differently
right on everything
no lawyers I don't know and I really
don't like lawyers like the lawyer way
of thinking
the lawyer way of thinking is asking the
question what can't you do not what can
you know
laughter most
this is really the last periscope guys
we don't be more next year my clean
the more rejection I feel like this is
the last one yeah tomorrow tomorrow we
take the letters off of the car
our tomorrow's the truth Commodus 37
just 37 yeah that you saw comma no but I
mean look grow next year we're really
well
that's better yep
, Maps
we're working on him working on him a
lot on the the upstairs team working on
localization and mapping we have an
internal server which has our maps on
them they're accurate to about a meter
right now we want to get that accuracy
down to 10 centimeters open-source as
much as we can
so this is my warning to all the
companies out there planning to erect a
seat by holding a bath
planning to spend a lot of money right
now to invest in
and building a map with like a dedicated
fleet of mapping cars we are going to
disrupt it
I don't even mean this like an
aggressive way I mean this a taillight
no don't be you don't end up like that
if you can't figure out a way to sort of
profit off of the mapping operation
itself you're going to lose we're
profiting that they have some other yeah
right source of other source of income
right um I mean it's possible for things
like Avery to succeed where at least
you're crowdsourcing it even if you are
paying the users yeah but we believe in
paying the users the value we add value
with the dash cam sometimes I think we
add a lot of value with a pilot
all the updated maps are super data that
super broke that server broke there's no
incentive to fix that um what we're
doing Maps much more regionally now
we're trying to make the maps like
really good in one region and then we'll
get a probably open source like that
region we have lane signs and curves and
they'll all be accurate to like 10
centimeters
ah I think I mean we think of Schiffer
the way we think of Schiffer in the
coming years Schiffer is like the remote
control for their car especially if you
have any on mountain and stuff
yeah a future we picture is something
like your friend text you the location
of the dress
say like forward do shiver to my comedy
on it'll show up and wheeze yeah you'll
start going it'll it'll show up in ways
and then alright you know what it's the
end of the year we're going to talk
about
ah
no we're not gonna talk about it about
any burning paradigms
our speak
I honestly I don't know if we could see
we do want to make a cop cop net we
region
I don't cops who are pulled over on the
side of the room trying to uh-oh cops
when they're moving to don't when
they're moving - yeah
based on
you look at the car right similar
computer so Mary people see cops right
sure we're good love all of our for
an open pilot network to report back
we're all the police already two ways
yeah we could we could could you beat
that source two ways we can figure out a
way to kind of make that data I'm not
sure we're gonna contribute in two ways
I think we will try to make that
available in our apps I think this is
maybe the killer feature of Scheffer
yeah that will keep people like really
if we get out the best cop detector I
think this is how ways bootstrapped
yeah
now I'm saying about pigeons we're gonna
try to have some out the second or third
week in January to the top neon users
don't care if it's ultraviolet ship
applause top neon users and has to be a
neon opposite attacked
we plug into yarns we're gonna send some
out
get telemetry and then if the telemetry
looks good
so
you know what I would give for other
companies to periscopes like us
just like I just would be so happy daddy
really cool yeah boy and I was thinking
like like a lot of people emailed George
asking you know to be involved in how
many I some business blah blah blah well
like if you hopped on periscope and
started asking those questions like you
have access to George Hawks rattling
anyone out there wants to know yeah
actually like wanna negotiate on
periscope how cool the world would that
be if like you hear yeah you know Apple
buying Shazam on periscope you know like
imagine she Sam had a periscope right
and this is
in New York City just just some beat up
we go to the car and yeah
we can all do it we have it comes a
self-driving car awareness to a reunion
event
[Music]
but ya know I'm I do this thing all
right I get people reaching out to me a
lot kind of like investment analysis
firms and they want to pay me $500 for
an hour of my time to talk with me about
about the suspicious about the
autonomous vehicle space and I said it
has someone I'll do it if you could buy
me an HTC vive should be an HTC vive if
she c5 is $100 more
to be honest I'm sure they don't care
about the money
well I think I'd like for them reach out
to me and offer me this deal I think I
even had one offer me 750
and I said by me and she said five they
couldn't do it
because they're that bureaucratic HTC
five test is kind of a great test of who
you want to talk to
um so same thing with the periscopes
right if people email me and I'll send
me like four emails reaching out I just
ignore them I actually have some filters
to just set up to ignore them like
do you care or are you doing this as a
job if you can talk to us on periscope
and I'll beat you I'll get credibly
honest keep it simple and those are the
people we want to work with
yeah Papelbon Shazam on a periscope like
there's like secure jobs talking I just
posterity sake writing like it like
breaks down this
information excess that like maybe only
the media has right now yeah and then
the media presents it through their land
yes you too right you guys I was tax
person the usual sense you're what what
times person the year in 2006 enough
we series just work out them how many
other colors of us
I will rip it no scope is out there
choice $400 50 no but it gave me half of
it no one honestly if that's what I go
to jail for cutting out man yes the eyes
if you want to do it if you want to go
through these periscopes and analyze it
is engagements you're definitely based
on all about like how you train them
nets are a very powerful idea
I don't know like what it would even
mean for something to replace deep Nets
I think things will work with deep nets
I think we'll find better ways to train
them I think better learning is gonna be
a huge field fishing learning but we
still use optimizers like if using
stochastic gradient descent there is no
metal learning you talk about momentum
as meta learning but that's still very
very crude right what if you could learn
what your future weight updates would
would look like you can build predictive
models of the learner
this is not an original idea there's
people talking about it it's probably
people have done a lot more researchers
up on it than me and no kind of
yeah virtually Chris is like its owner
mistakes in Portland
yeah and also
all the data home
no trying to have rows and or lemons
wants to do it
they're kind of like user exact user
numbers we don't really share those kind
of things to detain
no chair model in the basement there's
25 GPUs in a cluster
on the cloud is kind of hard for budget
reasons
data access and we have
good set it up to all poles mesthri
train it out some of those maybe one
hundredths they got an AWS now next year
we moved to cloud training we're not
buying anymore hardware
wasn't so dark they were about to come
up on a cool spot from Missouri no
Mississippi was like a huge part of the
missus this scene is built right on the
Mississippi okay morning we got time
tomorrow the tour ends tonight folks
um because most statistics are very easy
to miss a temper
Oh
maybe resuming menus
you want to see this manoeuvre I think I
think you see the availability of
ride-sharing services increasing
property values in places where public
transportation doesn't access in cities
where like public transportation is
super common like New York people who
live like a 20 minute walk from the
nearest subway stop maybe their property
value has gone off
New York has cabs because they're good
experience right and they were never
that they were never overpriced they
would never sell they're not that
overpriced they take credit cards
they're clean
you don't generally get it oh my god are
you getting some cabs in s after you're
like this drivers on trunk guys had this
in Vegas to them like they're throwing
drunks and I'm like I could tell I never
had to New York I've never like gone
into a cab or I could tell them like
someone vomit in the Euro week ago the
clean either seeds a nice barrier it's a
good experience right and that's where
companies should be competing they
should be competing
a surge of music videos Asher cuz they
gave us free money
it was AWS and then answer gave us more
free money thanks Adam
to be honest it probably worked we
probably will end up sticking with Adam
because who's doing another migration
not the person who the migration last
time
yeah
carbon Patrick yeah I like their car
dealerships that another question no
just don't compete car dealerships don't
keep climbing your faxes won't getting
into the business of making cars is not
a great business to be in
you're gonna see the same thing with
folks notice that the people who made
phone make phones today are the same
people who are making phones you know
twenty years ago
for the most part
I think us apples off but they were
making I think iPods which is a similar
thing right but a lot of this sort of
like the Samsung's the LG's
same companies making cell phones
forever
Motorola hey you watch the Nokia's the
BlackBerry's top the same thing didn't
happen with the car manufacturers maybe
you'll see you'll see like the fourths
and for for Florida's who I don't have a
bright prognosis for if you think you
really don't want to get Foxconn where
they should be they make a great trap
it was quits a lot but can you download
your data on chipper yeah
there's gonna be the duck on banana guy
we could make exporting easier Bichette
and exporting a can David if exporting a
candidate will make expert videos from
Cabana as well we'd already save it like
I apparently you can't right-click on
the stream and click Save
I thought that worked because I'm sure
you can find some stream download or
tool and it'll work
for what you need a fee it's a town
motor it is I mean it's rate limited at
some points I don't know
and then we have a bunch of driving data
available from our research paper we do
on archive.org seven and a half hours we
know we're going in yeah exit to exit
typical no he'll navigate us - yeah
we're parking the car to sleep in a time
yeah next spot pilot River - exit - well
that's on the Missouri side yes - well
the Missouri side Wisconsin side
the actors we pass over into
trap
how many copies
yeah it's like depending on our energy
that's true back at girls too
the materials that like car companies
make within a car it's pretty limited
already so what you like to touch and
sit on
like the parts of the car that like Ford
makes is pretty limited probably make
like the body the seats no I mean look
you can make the same argument about
about LG writing the LG buys the process
of meet wall comm sure they have like
okay I've just I am like I don't think
people think that car isn't a bad way
hey I mean say with phone seven exactly
yeah it's the same phones like they buy
those hands up peace they buy a camera
module there's Tier one suppliers in a
lot of industries see I mean most things
in a car are made by or made by Tier one
suppliers the steering column is made by
life
like Bosch and certain columns cotton at
all yeah radars like my textile
divisions
continuously drive around
virtually Chris that's the fans question
no to be honest we probably wouldn't
accept it
like oh well yeah I mean that's why we
won't accept it right we've a we've
briefly worked with this with this
company and it just it doesn't work this
expectations aren't aligned if you're a
car company out there you literally want
to give us a car because you think we
are cool no strings attached I will
accept any car except the suit now I'll
even accept the Subaru I'm just kidding
to the question like like for you I'll
answer the question mark plan right now
is to really just continue with Honda's
Toyota's I'll probably get bored of this
plan mid next year because I'm
personally sick of driving around in
Madison Toyota's but the cynic is so
nice dude I used to drive her bass nice
car I went from like Benzes and Porsches
to like civics and some on doesn't
Toyota's just this is just me and my
personal life right but is this system
at the quality level where we can put it
in a Benz and feel good about it I don't
think so I think we have to get better
and when we get better we'll start
working in
I personally yo guys I want a
self-driving car right and you know
obviously the car that I would choose to
buy is not not one of these
if I was buying a car for my personal
life but
if this is your budget for a car these
are the best cars you're gonna find in
this Christ reach yea the rav4 has
really jumped up
a few spots
it's past year oh yeah yeah this is
apparently for a llama one car that's
here but no none of a1 so for a while it
was it was number three a while is
number three for like
the fiestas down there too
yes that's like 14 14 you can get a car
for me the fit is like 50 it's pretty
crazy how expensive these things yeah
well no I mean the real thing that's
crazy expensive his used cars yeah right
you're rolling you're willing to get
like no I gotta know what I bought by
the way what I bought a portion of and a
Mercedes I didn't play new Porsches and
Mercedes I bought used ones but Porsche
cost me 10 grand yeah there's a great
lots of fun car $110,000 car new use
cars a great deal you can probably buy
it
I sold it Honda Fit I sold it for 14
like that's the real do you feel like oh
I don't like I'm right here I'm happy
with the depreciation of the value of
the money I got on that car
oh it's like probably knives there's a
few problems of the Tesla first off they
aren't luxury cars despite a Model S
having the price tag of a luxury car I
feel like the interior and the ride
quality doesn't even match navigate for
Richard I doesn't
electric okay the acceleration is cool I
like the acceleration I really like the
responsiveness you know what kills me we
rent it out
we rented a Chevy Volt and they
literally delay the acceleration to try
to mimic a gasoline car you have so much
more power available to you in that
motor you deliberately make it black
it's disgusting I mean it's the only
explanation I have if that explanation
is wrong I would love to know but that
is certainly what it feels like but yeah
they certainly have this thing electric
cars called creep right right does they
get turned on give it to em City right
yeah dead zone let's tell them what we
really think about them we love you
scobie's even if you can't go peas our
belly bag probably like
No okay good now if you're driving
safely the truth is good safe driving
all cars can kind of be treated as a
second
our limits are steering torque limits
are breaking them it's our acceleration
limits are well within what any
production car begin
leave them in exit 2
it's exit 2 in the new stage it's not
the exits are going that way that's why
I say standard for that
I guess they restart this thing we saw
that though anywhere else no we did I
think they only restart when they change
the name of the fireman no no they
definitely restart to stay indefinitely
we start this tape the only question is
are they going up are they going down I
guess they start going up again well
yeah we're quite high 500 we didn't have
enough attention to see if that was true
all throughout the states but yeah they
do run into an interesting problem where
if like you have one that's descending
one the day seven you have to exit tubes
actually pretty close to each others
just in different states interesting
state coordination I bet you members of
state legislatures have spent a lot of
time discussing
well these are all federal
nothing school forever
propaganda used to be a lot more glaze
this is something the newest
this the band is called best friends
forever
episode Oh Eisenhower and Eisenhower
you know I think so true but right I was
like I was a bridge player he's like
real she's really like a political about
everything player player of games which
we still had that I like because he got
on the air and told the American people
about the dangers of the
military-industrial complex interesting
yeah it's great interview with
it's like
I have this machine that exists we need
to be weary of it yeah and then it kind
of
yeah
true inch later Truman made the decision
to drop the ball there about interviews
the Truman we're like they're talking
about you know do you really feel like
you made the right decision what about
all those lives in Truman's just like
look man you have no idea what it feels
like that made this decision
hey yeah me like all the people that
worked on the bomb pretty upset yeah
you can play out alternative histories
of what would've happened it was a
shout-out to Monty we're coming up on
what do you think of recursive neural
networks
wavenet kana stuff I wouldn't exactly
know what the term is it's hard to keep
all the terms straight I kind of just
see the NAP diagrams being drawn out and
they probably informational flow
I don't have to look into hell like more
where they are
oh you were the muscle car usage that's
great man I want a Hyperloop yeah I'm
not worried about these muscle guys
doing hey I'm honestly I'm excited by
these things I would love to live in a
better world with her Hyperloop
dude much for leaving in like two
million thanks you for joining us for
this trip it's been great having you on
the we're excited for more your videos
[Music]
thanks it
maybe we'll leave it with that Kofi's
we're going to the French island and
where we go from here nobody knows
see you in the new
my Scoobies thanks for joining us on
this trip processes a great afternoon